Congratulations!
You've successfully navigated the world of international
business.
You've registered, decided and listed what to sell, and made some
decisions about how to fulfill and ship your products all over the world.
Now
learn about the additional tools, support, and guidance Amazon has to help you
manage your international sales.
Selling internationally on Amazon requires you
provide customer support in the native language of that marketplace.
FBA
provides direct customer support for all fulfillment related questions in
the necessary languages.
Amazon also helps guide your business to make smart
choices about inventory and ways to optimize your product portfolio as well
as providing self-service tools for determining your pricing and our
advertising and marketing tools help you reach customers with targeted ads that
boost sales and grow your presence.
We can also help you get paid in the
currency of your choice.
Watch as your international business takes off with
Amazon Global Selling.
For a list of the products and services available through
Amazon Global Selling, click the link below.